export const categoriesData = [
  {
    title: "Категория 1",
    raiting: 0,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: "Вопрос 1",
        answer: "Ответ 1",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: "Вопрос 2",
        answer: "Ответ 2",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: "Вопрос 3",
        answer: "Ответ 3",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: "Вопрос 4",
        answer: "Ответ 4",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Категория 2",
    raiting: 0,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 5,
        question: "Вопрос 1",
        answer: "Ответ 1",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: "Вопрос 2",
        answer: "Ответ 2",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "Вопрос 3",
        answer: "Ответ 3",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: "Вопрос 4",
        answer: "Ответ 4",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Категория 3",
    raiting: 0,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 9,
        question: "Вопрос 1",
        answer: "Ответ 1",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: "Вопрос 2",
        answer: "Ответ 2",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: "Вопрос 3",
        answer: "Ответ 3",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: "Вопрос 4",
        answer: "Ответ 4",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Категория 4",
    raiting: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 13,
        question: "Вопрос 1",
        answer: "Ответ 1",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 3,
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: "Вопрос 2",
        answer: "Ответ 2",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: "Вопрос 3",
        answer: "Ответ 3",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 2,
      },
      {
        id: 16,
        question: "Вопрос 4",
        answer: "Ответ 4",
        reviewSent: false,
        raiting: 0,
      },
    ],
  },
];
